{
    "id": "c69e8fe1e1f940ff84d35baaeda938cc",
    "title": "Rob And Steal",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "642c361c5c92468fb86611399c159f83",
            "title": "Rob And Steal",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "To get rich quickly, they decided to ........................... a bank.",
                    "description": "The object of rob is the person or the place that was the victim of the robbery.",
                    "answers": [
                        "steal",
                        "rob"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Someone ................................ a painting from the museum.",
                    "description": "The object of steal is the item stolen.",
                    "answers": [
                        "robbed",
                        "stole"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The boy complained that somebody had ............................. his bicycle.",
                    "description": "You steal something.",
                    "answers": [
                        "robbed",
                        "stolen"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Someone ................................... my phone on the train.",
                    "description": "You steal something. You rob someone.",
                    "answers": [
                        "robbed",
                        "stole"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The travelers were ................................... at knifepoint.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "robbed",
                        "stolen"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She accused me of ................................. her money.",
                    "description": "You steal an object. You rob a person or place. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "stealing",
                        "robbing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The bandits ................................. the travelers.",
                    "description": "You rob a person.",
                    "answers": [
                        "robbed",
                        "stole"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The thieves ................................ jewelry worth thousands of dollars.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "stole",
                        "robbed"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Someone ............................. me on the train.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "stole",
                        "robbed"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He was arrested for ………………………… the policeman’s helmet.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "stealing",
                        "robbing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The bank was ……………………….. last night.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "stolen",
                        "robbed"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The house was ……………………… while the family was on vacation.",
                    "description": "To talk about a house we use burgle.",
                    "answers": [
                        "stolen",
                        "robbed",
                        "burgled"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}